(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a while.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: To all visitors
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
2次販売グッズ
Secondary Sales Goods
メッセージをお寄せいただきありがとうございます！
Thank you for sending your messages!
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
For production reasons, please be aware of flashing lights.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK!
た・く・さ・ん！
So-ma-ny!
たくさんの素敵なショート動画ありがとうございました！
Thank you for the many wonderful short videos!
君のこと大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き！
I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you so much!
溢れるこの愛きっと止まらない
This overflowing love surely won't stop
ぜひ最後までお楽しみください！
Please enjoy until the end!
I-I-I-I love you 君に
I-I-I-I love you, to you
素敵なショート動画ありがとうございました！
Thank you for the wonderful short videos!
I I I I love you
もっと もっと
More, more
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want
ゆめみるハートがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming heart goes hop hop hop
あなたに落ちてあーりゃりゃ
Falling for you, oh my
こんなになってもいまだに抜け出せない
Even like this, I still can't get out
ぜひ「あいあいあいらぶゆー」を使って動画を作ってみてください！
Please try making videos using "I I I Love You"!
どうしたものかな ぬいぬいぬい
What should I do? Nui nui nui
助けて君たち アホイホイ
Save me, everyone, Ahoy-hoy
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more
好きなだけ愛してね
Please love me as much as you want
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon...
Sponsors 協賛
Sponsors
どアニメ宣言！
The Ultimate Anime Declaration!
アニメにハマって、歌いたくなっちゃった。
I got hooked on anime, and now I just want to sing!
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて...
To be able to sing karaoke while watching scenes of my fave...
尊すぎてツライっ！
It's so precious it hurts!
歌いたい曲見つけよう！
Let's find the songs you want to sing!
ジョイサウンド！
JOYSOUND!
どアニメ宣言！
The Ultimate Anime Declaration!
全国のアミューズメント施設にてホロライブ3期生プライズ順次展開中！
Hololive 3rd Generation prizes are now arriving at amusement centers nationwide!
吉野家でごはんしょ♪
Let's eat at Yoshinoya♪
んま〜
Mmm~
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。
Taste the true passion of the original. Please enjoy.
牛丼は吉野家。
When it comes to beef bowls, it's Yoshinoya.
やっぱこれだな。
Nothing beats this.
ホロライブ3期生 ミニCDコレクション
Hololive 3rd Generation Mini CD Collection
きゅるるん大作戦 ～最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ～
Operation Kyururun: The Ultimate Idols, You Have to Support Them!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: To all attendees
2次販売グッズ
2nd Round Merchandise
本日は
Today,
ホロライブ...
Hololive...
hololive 3rd Generation Live きゅるるん大作戦〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜に ご来場いただき ありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to hololive 3rd Generation Live: Kyururun Daisakusen ~The Strongest Idols, You Can't Help But Stan!~
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the live show to the end, we have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は、固くお断りいたします。
The use of cameras, recording devices, or video equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮ください。
The venue is non-smoking. Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は 無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
Should you feel unwell, please don't overexert yourself and inform a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他の皆んなの迷惑になったり、
Moshing, diving, throwing objects onto the stage, or any behavior that disturbs others
公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
or interferes with the show is strictly forbidden. Please follow the rules and have a great time!
すごいね。聞こえるね。うん。
That's amazing. We can hear them. Yeah.
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合があります。
Additionally, cameras for video streaming and photography will be in the venue, and the audience may be captured in the footage.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは #きゅるるん大作戦Day2 です。
The official hashtag for the live show is #KyururunDaisakusenDay2.
ハッシュタグを使って、たくさん盛り上げてください！(盛り上げてね！)
Please use the hashtag and help us build the hype! (Build the hype!)
それでは、開演まであと少しです。君たちの声をいっぱい聞かせてください！
Now then, there's just a little bit left until the show starts. Let us hear your voices!
そして、今からちょっと 3期生で円陣を組もうと思っているんですが... えっと、マイクを通さずやりますので、
And now, we 3rd Gen members are going to do a huddle... but we'll be doing it without mics,
ちょっと静かにして、あの... 皆んな耳を澄ませていただければと思います。
so if everyone could please be quiet and... listen closely.
耳を澄ませて！お願いします！
Listen closely! Please!
いくんで、ちょっと... しーんと待っててくださいね。(静かにね) いきます！
Here we go, so please... wait in silence. (Keep it quiet.) Here goes!
ぺこ！
Peko!
マリン！
Marine!
フレア！
Flare!
ノエル！
Noel!
我ら！ホロライブ！
We are! hololive!
三期生！
3rd Generation!
いくぞー！
Let's go!
おー！
Ohhh!
こんぺこ！
兎田ぺこら
Konpeko!
Usada Pekora
不知火フレア
Shiranui Flare
こんまっする
白銀ノエル
Konmassuru
Shirogane Noel
Ahoy!
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
きゅるるん大作戦
〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
Operation Kyururun
~The Strongest Idols, You've Got to Support Them~
超アイドル級のガールは欲張り
Super-idol class girls are greedy
笑いあって もっと可愛くなる
Laughing together, we'll become even cuter
Oh yeah yeah
遠回りのようで近道で
It seems like a detour, but it's a shortcut
三期生なのに家族みたいで
Even though we're the 3rd Gen, we're like family
るるらく アラカルテーション
Lulu-luck a-la-cart-ation
くるらく せいえっとステーション
Kururaku say it station
喜怒哀楽をちゃ足してさ
Adding a mix of all our emotions
デカくなっていきたいよね
We want to become even bigger
でも小さなことも大事にして
But we'll cherish the small things too
一歩ずつ 追い風受けて
Step by step, with the wind at our backs
楽しんでくれるのが嬉しい
We're happy when you enjoy it
これからのエンターテイナー
The entertainers of the future
後ろまで見えてるよ
We can see all the way to the back
画面の向こうも届いてる
We're reaching you behind the screen too
光の海を泳ごう
Let's swim through this sea of light
超アイドル級のガールは欲張り
Super-idol class girls are greedy
愛されたいし
We want to be loved
夢を見てたい
We want to keep dreaming
君とじゃなきゃヤダ！
It has to be with you!
絶好調です！
We're in top form!
狙い撃ちで
Taking aim...
君にウインク
...and winking at you
やっぱ超絶のガールで めちゃハッピー
As transcendent girls, we're super happy
お嫁もしたいし
We want to be brides
声も出したい
We want to shout out
叶っちゃう！やったー！
It's coming true! Yay!
先頭走る 無邪気に君と
Running at the front, innocently with you
笑いあって もっと可愛くなる
Laughing together, we'll become even cuter
Oh yeah yeah
せっかくだから
Since we're here
やり切りたいし
We want to give it our all
乗り越える壁 とてもデカい
The walls to overcome are so huge
将来うんとエンタメで
In the future, with plenty of entertainment
君が思ってるよりずっと
Much more than you think
君のことを思ってる
We're thinking of you
どうかな？
How about it?
焦がれた
The dreams we yearned for
夢には近づけてるかな？
Are we getting any closer to them?
声の限りがあるから
Because our voices have a limit
頑張れるんだ
We can work our hardest
聞かせて！
Let us hear you!
1 2 3 4!
最最高級のガールは幸せ
Super-duper high-class girls are happy
愛されていて
Being loved
伸び代あって
With room to grow
下向くとかヤダ！
I hate looking down!
テンポアップし
Picking up the tempo
続けていきたい
We want to keep going
景色へ
To that scenery
世界にダッシュ！
Dashing to the world!
限界呼び覚ませ
Awaken your limits
今すぐ達成
Achieve it right now
皆で作ってく... イェーイ！
We'll make it all together... Yay!
後半戦も盛り上がっていくぞー！
Second half, let's keep this energy up!
君たち まだまだ声 出せますよねー！
You guys can still scream louder, right?!
揺らいでも頑張っちゃう
Even if I waver, I'll do my best
褒められて伸びるは分かってるよね
You know I thrive on praise, right?
この負荷が宝物
This burden is a treasure
寝ちゃわないわよ笑
I won't fall asleep, haha
君と一緒に！
Together with you!
超アイドル！天道ガールは欲張り
Super Idol! Tendo girl is greedy
愛されたいし夢だってみたい君とじゃなきゃやだ
I want to be loved and I want to dream,
it has to be with you
絶対絶好調です！願い撃ちで君にウインク
I'm in top form! Winking at you with my wishes
やっぱ天道ガールでめっちゃハッピー
Being a Tendo girl makes me so happy
あれもしたいしこれもしたいし叶っちゃう
I want to do this and that, and it's all coming true
全力疾走！もちろん君と笑い合って
Sprinting full speed! Of course, laughing together
もっと可愛くなる
I'll become even cuter
どこまででも行けちゃう気がする
I feel like I can go anywhere
Oh yeah yeah
今日はこのままさよならじゃないよ
Today isn't a goodbye just like this
手を取ってくれたなら
If you would take my hand
秘密も眠りにつくような夜に
In a night where even secrets go to sleep
君を連れて行くよ
I'll take you away
それは例えば遠く離れてたって
For example, even if we are far apart
手を繋いでいられるような
Like we can still hold hands
奇跡のような話をしよう
Let's talk about something like a miracle
窓は開けておいて
Keep the window open
今日までを思い出して
Think back on everything until today
一つ一つ並べたら
If we line them up one by one
明日の雨が気になりだして
I start to worry about tomorrow's rain
どうも眠れないみたいだ
It seems I can't sleep
変わりたくないことや
Things I don't want to change
変わらなきゃいけないことも
And things that must change
少し忘れたまま窓の外眺めていたんだ
Leaving them forgotten for a bit,
I was looking out the window
Ah...
雨が降り出すその前に
Before the rain starts to fall
君のところまで行けるような気がして目を閉じみたんだ
I feel like I can make it to where you are,
so I tried closing my eyes
そして...
And then...
このまま遠くへと行こう
Let's go far away just like this
手を取ってくれるかな
Will you take my hand?
秘密も眠りにつくような夜を
Through the night where even secrets go to sleep
君と泳いでいくよ
I'll swim with you
街の明かりが消えるたびに笑って
Laughing every time the city lights go out
路地裏で抱き合うような
Like hugging in a back alley
馬鹿みたいな話をしよう
Let's talk about something silly
窓は開けておいて
Keep the window open
聞こえる？
Can you hear it?
聞こえる
I can hear it
次はマリン！
Next is Marine!
キミたち！2日目も盛り上がっていきますよ！
You guys! Let's keep the excitement
going for Day 2!
どっちが好きよのよ！
Which one do you like?!
なんとかかんないかな
Can't we do something about this?
Lavi lavi
隣のあいつが邪魔だな
That guy next to me is in the way
ダメダメダメダメ
No no no no
全知全能絶対
Omniscient, omnipotent, absolute
どわどわ違うな
No, that's different
なんだって競争
Everything is a competition
苦手だそういうの
I'm not good at that kind of thing
ランデブーマシン むちむちマシン
Rendezvous Machine, muchi muchi machine
内緒シークレット ペコペコシルエット
Secret secret, peko peko silhouette
あの子に負けない
I won't lose to that girl
今更ジェラシー
Jealousy even now
欲張りだ 逆張りか
Greedy, or just contrary?
してやりますわ
I'll show you
Oh!
言わなきゃ伝わってる
It's understood without saying
ああでもないこうでもない
Neither this nor that
やめにしましょう
Let's stop that
連なる My My My My
Chained My My My My
引きたくない 言い訳バニー
I don't want to pull back, Excuse Bunny
ジレンマの憂鬱
Melancholy of dilemma
だんだんたん
Dan dan tan
ハニバニダリダリ
Honey Bunny Dari Dari
マジな話どっちどっちが好きなのよ！
Seriously, which one do you like?!
ダメダメダメダメ 余所見しないで
No no no no, don't look away
ダメダメダメダメ 抜け出したい
No no no no, I want to break free
今日は私の法 でしょでしょ
Today is my law, right, right?
どうして反対方向 One Two!
Why is it the opposite direction? One Two!
言い訳バニー
Excuse Bunny
吐き出したい　言い訳はなに？
What's the excuse you want to spit out?
地団駄の憂鬱　ふたんだった
Stamping feet, the melancholy was a burden.
ハニバニダリダリ　マジな話
Honey bunny dari dari, seriously.
どっち　どっち　が好きなのよ　ハイ！
Which one, which one do you like? Hey!
ダメダメダメ　よそ見しないで
No no no, don't look away.
ダメダメダメ　もう逃げ出したい？
No no no, do you want to run away already?
覚悟やるしかない！
No choice but to be prepared!
所信表明　反対方向
Declaration of intent, opposite direction.
ハイ！
Hey!
WANTED!
言い訳あり
With an excuse.
そばにいて　言い訳あり
Stay by my side, with an excuse.
次はぺこら〜！
Next is Pekora~!
全力ジャンピング！イッツ・オール・オッケー！
Full power jumping! It's All Okay!
でも一歩を踏み出したくなくって
But I didn't want to take a step forward.
歌いながら気の向く方へ
Singing along to wherever I feel like.
迷ってるの？　冒険してるの？
Are you lost? Are you on an adventure?
それはみんな次第！
That's up to everyone!
まだまだ楽しみ足りない
Still haven't had enough fun.
でもでも時間が足りない
But but, not enough time.
ワクワクする明日へ
To an exciting tomorrow.
思い切って　張り切って　前向いて　さあ進もう！
Taking a leap, being enthusiastic, looking forward, let's go!
せーの！
Ready, go!
歌って本気で
Sing seriously.
ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey!
演じきっちゃえ
Play it out completely.
ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey!
欲張っちゃいくらいで
Just about being greedy.
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's All Okay!
早起きよりも
Rather than waking up early.
ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey!
勇気を出して
Show some courage.
ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey!
なんとかなっちゃうはずだから
Because it should work out somehow.
ピンチはチャンスになるからさ
Because a pinch becomes a chance.
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's All Okay!
みんなで笑えば無敵だね
If we laugh together, we're invincible.
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's All Okay!
何だって全力で
With full power in everything.
ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey!
走り抜けちゃって
Run through it.
ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey!
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's go with straightforward feelings.
ホップステップで飛び出そう！
Let's leap out with a hop, step!
なかなかお布団から出られない日もある
There are days when I can't quite get out of bed.
でも明日から　そう明日から
But from tomorrow, yes, from tomorrow.
本気を出すんだ！
I'll get serious!
日が沈むまで　日が暮れるまで
Until the sun sets, until the day ends.
無邪気な感じで
In an innocent way.
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's All Okay!
早起きよりも
Rather than waking up early.
ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey!
勇気を出して
Show some courage.
ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey!
なんとかなっちゃうはずだから
Because it should work out somehow.
ピンチはチャンスになるからさ
Because a pinch becomes a chance.
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's All Okay!
みんなで笑えば無敵だね
If we laugh together, we're invincible.
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's All Okay!
何だって全力で
With full power in everything.
ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey!
走り抜けちゃって
Run through it.
ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey!
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's go with straightforward feelings.
ホップステップで飛び出そう！
Let's leap out with a hop, step!
イェーイ！
Yee-haw!
最後はノエル！
Lastly, Noel!
はーい！みんなー！シャッフルメドレー、最後まで盛り上がっていくぞー！
Hi! Everyone! Let's get pumped for the shuffle medley until the very end!
苦い恋の果て　残されたデドコロ不明のカネの山
At the end of a bitter love, a pile of money of unknown origin was left behind.
アイツの気配がするもの、未練ばかりで食えやしない
Things that reek of him, I can't stomach them with all these lingering attachments.
私は生きながら　化けて出る鏡の前で早変わり
While alive, I transform quickly in front of the mirror, coming out as a ghost.
バイバイ仮面でどうかしら　今宵も一暴れ
How about a "Bye-bye Mask"? Going on a rampage again tonight.
踊れ踊り踊れ　乱れ髪弾む胸
Dance, dance, dance. Disheveled hair, bouncing chest.
ドクメイの罠に酔いしれて
Intoxicated by the trap of an alias.
SHAY SPOT! SHAY SPOT! SHAY SPOT!　愛をみなー
Shay spot! Shay spot! Shay spot! Behold the love!
バイヤ　バイヤ　バッパヤバイ　バイバイ仮面は大富豪
Baiya baiya bappaya bad, Bye-bye Mask is a millionaire.
バイヤ　バッパヤバイ　黄金の蝶舞い上がれ
Baiya bappaya bad, the golden butterfly, soar up.
ホーヤ　ホーヤ　踊れよ　散財万歳　恋シャワー
Hoya hoya, dance! Hurray for squandering! Love shower!
セーナ　セーナ　お生きろよ　瞬間クライマックス
Sena sena, live on! Momentary climax!
浮世忘れて更ける　Dancing high high high, higher buyer
Forgetting the transient world, it deepens. Dancing high high high, higher buyer.
ディスコティックイイ　バイバイ仮面
Discotheque good, Bye-bye Mask.
黄金の蝶舞い上がれ
Golden butterfly, soar high
吠えろ魔法を踊れよ
Howl, dance to the magic
三才万歳恋シャワー
Three-year banzai, love shower
せーの、お生きろよ
One, two, live on
瞬間クライマックス
Climax of the moment
浮世忘れてぶっ飛ばせ ハイハイヤー
Forget the fleeting world and blast off! High, higher!
ディスコディスコ食い パイパイ仮面
Disco, disco, eat... Pai Pai Kamen
ディスコディスコ食い
Disco, disco, eat...
パイパイ仮面
Pai Pai Kamen
Noel
イェーイ！
Yay!
Day 2!
じゃあ早速自己紹介からしていきましょうか
Well then, let's start with introductions right away.
していきましょう
Let's do it.
じゃあみんなぺこら久しぶりのあの挨拶行くからわかるよねみんな！
Alright everyone, I'm going to do that greeting after a long time, you know which one, right?!
あの挨拶だよ
That greeting.
どの挨拶だ？
Which one?
あれだ！あれしかない！
That one! It can only be that one!
行くぞ！ドンドンガドンドン...
Here we go! Don-don-ga-don-don...
全VTuber一... 全VT...
All VTuber... All VT...
大丈夫か？
Are you okay?
もう一回ね、もう一回ね、いきます！
One more time, one more time. Here I go!
ドンドンガドンドン！全VTuber一超絶可愛いのは誰だ？！
Don-don-ga-don-don! Who's the most super-extra cute of all VTubers?!
ドンドンガドンドーン！
Don-don-ga-don-doon!
ぺこら様ー！
Pekora-sama!
やっとできました！ありがとう！
I finally did it! Thank you!
次はフレア！
Next is Flare!
はい！じゃあフレアは「はいダーリン！」って言うので...
Yes! So, I'll say "Hi Darling!" so...
「はいハニー！」って返してください！
Please reply with "Hi Honey!"
はいダーリン！
Hi Darling!
はいハニー！
Hi Honey!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ホロライブ3期生不知火フレアです！そして！
I'm Shiranui Flare from Hololive 3rd Generation! And next!
はい！えー、どうしようかな今日。
Yes! Um, what should I do today?
あ、じゃあコンまっするって言うから普通にコンまっするで...
Oh, I'll say "Kon-massuru" so just normally "Kon-massuru"...
牛丼はいいのか？
Is beef bowl okay?
あ、牛丼もね... 牛丼はまあ... あ、やばいやばい...
Oh, beef bowl too... Well, beef bowl is... Oh, no, no...
行くぞ！せーの！
Here we go! One, two!
コンまっするー！
Kon-massuru!
はい、ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルです！
Yes, I'm Shirogane Noel from Hololive 3rd Generation!
イェーイ！
Yay!
君たち、本物のパイパイ仮面は誰？！
You guys, who is the real Pai Pai Kamen?!
マリンー！
Marine!
本物のパイパイ仮面... なんですけども、昨日からさ、
I'm the real Pai Pai Kamen... but since yesterday,
ぺこらに船長とられるしノエルにパイパイ仮面乗っ取られるし...
Pekora took the Captain title and Noel took over Pai Pai Kamen...
本物のパイパイ仮面奪われたわけです。
My real Pai Pai Kamen title was stolen.
悲しい...
How sad...
ということでね、はい！ホロライブ3期生宝鐘海賊団船長、
Anyway, yes! I'm the Captain of the Houshou Pirates,
宝鐘マリンです！
Houshou Marine!
ついにDay 2！イェーイ！
Finally, Day 2! Yay!
なんか、昨日と衣装違くない？
Wait, aren't the outfits different from yesterday?
分かりましたか皆さん！
Did you notice, everyone?!
悪魔になっちゃった！
I've turned into a devil!
天使から悪魔っぽくなってしまったかな？
I wonder if I went from angel to devil-ish?
実はこれ初めて公開するんですよね！
Actually, this is the first time we're revealing this!
みんなびっくりしたかな？
Was everyone surprised?
可愛い！
Cute!
でも悪魔なんか結構マリンは小悪魔系で売ってるんで
But as for the devil look, Marine sells herself as the little devil type,
かなりシナジーあるかなって
so I think it has great synergy.
ぺこらも小悪魔系で売ってるから...
Pekora is also selling herself as the little devil type...
お前らは何だ！
What are you guys?!
天使と悪魔どっちが好き君たち？
Which do you like better, angels or devils?
あ、確かに！
Oh, true!
ペンライトの色とかで...
With penlight colors...
じゃあ、悪魔派は赤、天使派は白！
Then, the devil faction is red, and the angel faction is white!
皆さん変えてください！掲げてください！
Everyone, please change them! Hold them up!
若干赤が多いか？
Is there slightly more red?
あれ、悪魔の方が人気？
Wait, are devils more popular?
でもなんか結構半々かも！
But it might be pretty half and half!
じゃあ今日いいよね、悪魔な感じも
Then today is great, the devil vibe too.
Day 1に引き続きバンドも生演奏となってます！
Continuing from Day 1, the band is also performing live!
いいですね。本当にかっこいいですねこれね。
Looking good. These outfits are really cool, aren't they?
最高！
The best!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
嬉しいです。
I'm so happy.
そして配信のコメントももちろん見てます！
And of course, we're reading the stream comments too!
見てるよー！みんな！
We see you! Everyone!
もう、もちろん会場のみんなももちろん集まってるよー！
And of course, everyone at the venue is gathered here too!
集まってるよー！
You're all here!
見てるよー！
We see you!
みんな素敵。
Everyone looks wonderful.
気合の入った、推し活ファッションしてきてくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming in your pumped-up "oshi" fan fashion!
ありがとう！ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you so much!
最高、最高ですよ。
It's the best, simply the best.
最高ですね。いやもうちょっぱなね、シャッフルメドレーでしたけども！
It's great. We started off with a shuffle medley right away!
最高ですよ！やばかったよね！
It was amazing! That was wild, wasn't it?
アツアツになったよね。
Things really heated up.
アゲアゲ！
Getting hyped!
でもですね！なんとですね！ここまでで！
But everyone! Surprisingly! At this point!
えっ！？
Eh!?
冒頭無料チラ見せが終了となります！
The free sneak peek section at the beginning is now over!
うそぺこー！そんなー！
No way-peko! Oh no!
嘘でしょー！？そんなことある！？
You're kidding!? How can that be!?
嘘ぺこでしょ、今の！
You're joking, right-peko!?
そうなんですね。嘘ではないぺこです。
That's how it is. I'm not kidding-peko.
そうだよね。みんな見たいと思ってくれてると思うから、
Right. I think everyone still wants to watch, so...
概要欄に配信チケットリンクあるので、今ポチポチっと買ってみてください！
There's a link for streaming tickets in the description, so please go click and buy one now!
お願いします！
Please do!
後悔させない！今日はすごい！
We won't let you regret it! Today is amazing!
今日もまた一段と凄くなってるから！
It's even more incredible today!
もうぶち上げぶち上げで準備してますから。
We've prepared to get everyone super hyped up.
DAY1とは違ったまた盛り上がり、
It's a different kind of excitement from Day 1...
もう君たち、君たちも今日超ぶち上がりなんで！
And all of you, you're going to be super hyped today too!
頑張って最後まで息切れしないように、ぶち上がってください！
Try your best not to run out of breath and keep the hype going until the end!
最高潮までしっかり声出してね！
Make sure to shout at the top of your lungs!
そして配信で楽しんでる人は、配信ハッシュタグ「きゅるるん大作戦DAY2」にいっぱい呟いてください！
And those enjoying the stream, please tweet a lot using the hashtag #KyururunDaisakusenDAY2!
お願いします！
Please do!
はあ、はあ。ふう。
*Panting*
ドキドキするね。そろそろいいですか？行きますか！
I'm so nervous. Is everyone ready? Let's go!
次の曲に行ってもいいでしょうか！？
Can we move on to the next song!?
行っちゃいましょう！
Let's do it!
それではですね、次の曲はなんと私からスタートさせていただきます！いいですか！
Well then, for the next segment, I'll be the one starting things off! Are you ready!
おー！何が来るの！？なんだろうなんだろう！
Oh! What's coming!? I wonder what it is!
じゃあ次の曲いきましょう！
Then, let's go to the next song!
フレアメドレー！
Flare Medley!
おー！
Oh!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
本編の配信チケットは概要欄のリンクより絶賛販売中！
Streaming tickets for the main show are currently on sale via the link in the description!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.